<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="invalid_phone_number">Invalid phone number</string>
    <string name="otp_cannot_be_blank">OTP cannot be blank</string>
    <string name="invalid_phone_number_format">Invalid phone number format</string>
    <string name="otp_send_failure">Failed to send OTP</string>
    <string name="store_not_found_info">Store Not Found </string>
    <string name="otp_verification_failure">Unable to Verify OTP</string>
    <string name="device_attached_error">Device Attached to another store</string>
    <string name="registration_error">Registration Error. Phone number already registered with another Snapbizz Product. Please use a different phone number.</string>
    <string name="no_users_from_server">No Users From Server</string>
    <string name="login_wrong_password">Wrong Password</string>
    <string name="login_no_user_found">No User Found</string>
    <string name="login_failure">Unable to Login</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="unable_to_get_users">Failed to fetch latest users list</string>
    <string name="resend_otp">Resend</string>
    <string name="otp_sent">Otp Sent Successfully</string>
    <string name="sync_completed">Sync Completed</string>

    <string name="registration_error_prefix">Registration Error</string>
    <string name="registration_title">DD Registration</string>
    <string name="owner_details">Owner Details</string>
    <string name="owner_name">Owner Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="store_details">Store Details</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="store_name">Store Name</string>
    <string name="store_phone_number">Store Phone Number</string>
    <string name="zip_code">Zip Code</string>
    <string name="gstin_number">GSTIN Number</string>
    <string name="state">State</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="pos_id">POS ID</string>
    <string name="proceed">Proceed</string>
    <string name="central_portal_token">Unable to get token</string>



    <string name="agreement_string">
\n\nBY INSTALLING OR USING THIS SOFTWARE AND ANY APPLICATIONS USED IN
CONJUNCTION WITH THIS SOFTWARE (“SOFTWARE”) YOU ARE AGREEING TO BE
BOUND BY ALL OF THE TERMS SET FORTH BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE
TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT, DO NOT INSTALL OR USE THE SOFTWARE..

\n\nLimited License. SnapBizz CloudTech Pte. Ltd, the licensor of the Software (“We” or “Licensor”),
grants you a non-exclusive limited license to install the object code version of
the Software on one device and to use the Software on such device. All rights not expressly
granted are reserved by the Licensor.

 \n\nPrivacy Policy. We encourage you to review our privacy policy which can be found at bottom
of the page ("SnapBizz Privacy Policy"). By agreeing to this End User License Agreement
you are also agreeing to our Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy governs the collection, use
and disclosure of information we collect from you. The information we collect is stored and
processed by us on servers in India and potentially other countries. By installing the Software
you consent to any such transfer of your information outside your country and/or outside the
country where you use or have installed the Software.

\n\nRestrictions. You agree not to reproduce, modify, make derivative works or distribute the
Software to any third party. You agree not to decompile, disassemble or reverse engineer
the Software. You agree not to (i) remove any copyright or other proprietary notice from the
Software, or (ii) rent, lease, lend, upload, host, sell, or sublicense the Software, in whole or in
part.

\n\nOwnership. You agree that the Licensor and its licensors retain all right, title and interest in
and to the Software and has unconditional right to lock-out or disable the software. You agree to
erase the Software from your wireless device upon receipt of notice.

\n\nUsage &amp; Subscription. Free Trial Period - This application is offered with a free trial from
the date of registration. Once the trial period is over, you will only be able to continue using
the application by upgrading the same in the in-app purchases and paying the subscription fee for
additional usage. If you fail to pay for the additional usage, your account will be frozen and
inaccessible until payment is made.

\n\nUpgrades/Downgrades. Any upgrade/downgrades in plan level, will result in new rate being
charged from the date of upgradation/down-gradation. Downgrading your plan may cause the loss of
features.  The Company does not accept any liability for this loss.

\n\nTermination. This Agreement shall terminate immediately, without notice, if you fail to comply
with any material term of this Agreement. Upon termination you agree to immediately erase the
Software from your device. Termination is in addition to and not in lieu of any other rights and
remedies Licensor may have.

\n\nNo Support. Neither Licensor nor its licensors are obligated to provide any maintenance,
technical or other support for the Software.
\nDisclaimer of Warranty. THE SOFTWARE IS LICENSED TO YOU “AS IS.” LICENSOR AND
ITS LICENSORS DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES REGARDING THE APPLICATION,
WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS, MERCHANTABILITY
AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.

\n\nLimitation of Liability. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE
LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL THE LICENSOR OR ITS LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY
CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE, INDIRECT OR
DIRECT DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THE APPLICATION
(INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOST DATA OR LOST PROFITS), EVEN IF THE
LICENSOR HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

\n\nExport. The Software is subject to the export control laws and regulations of the Singapore
Government and other jurisdictions. You agree to comply with all such laws and regulations.

\n\nU.S. Government End Users. This section only applies to the U.S. Government or if you are
or are acting on behalf of an agency or instrumentality of the U.S. Government. The Software
is “commercial software” developed exclusively at private expense. Pursuant to FAR 12.212 or
DFARS 227 7202 and their successors, as applicable, use, reproduction and disclosure of the
Software is governed by the terms of this agreement.

\n\nMiscellaneous. The United Nations Convention on Contracts for the Sale of International
Goods does not apply to this agreement. If any provision hereof is held illegal, invalid or
unenforceable, in whole or in part, such provision shall be modified to the minimum extent
necessary to make it legal, valid and enforceable, and the legality, validity and enforceability
of all other provisions of this agreement shall not be affected thereby. This agreement
constitutes the entire agreement between you and the Licensor regarding its subject matter and
supersedes any prior agreement, whether written or oral, relating to the subject matter of this
agreement. No modification or alteration of this agreement will be valid except in writing signed
by you and the Licensor. SnapBizz CloudTech Pte. Ltd is an intended beneficiary of, and has
the right to enforce, the terms and conditions of this agreement that relate to or affect SnapBizz
CloudTech Pte. Ltd.

\n\nSnapBizz Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use and disclosure of
your information through our mobile application service (“SnapBizz Services”). When using
our service you agree to this Privacy Policy. SnapBizz Services are provided by SnapBizz
CloudTech Pte. Ltd, a company headquartered and incorporated in Singapore (“we”, “us”, and
“our”).

\n\n1. Data we collect

a. Information You Provide to SnapBizz
an account. The information SnapBizz will collect about you and your business includes:
business owner name (first name, middle name, and last name), date of birth, pan number,
mobile number, landline number, address, pin code, business name, business license number,
date the license number is valid until, business category, business address, pin code, and
contact number. If you are required to create a password, you should choose one that is known
only by you.

b. Information About Your Customer
your obligation to appropriately inform your customer how you will be using the information,
including if you will be sending offers or advertisements to their phones via SMS.

c. General Usage Information Collected
SnapBizz Services requires you to register and provide us information to create
SnapBizz Services may allow you to enter information about your customer. It is
We’ll collect information about how you use our SnapBizz Services such as: (i)
the services that you access, (ii) information about the links and/or advertisements that you
click, (iii) the frequency and duration of use, and (iv) the fact that you use certain features or
functions. We will use this information in order to provide and improve our SnapBizz Services.
Additional information that will be collected includes monthly sales stats and details and pricing
of products sold in retail shop. The information you provide will be stored on our or a third party
service providers’ servers.

d. Information You Submit
If you voluntarily submit information to us - for example, if you participate in
a survey, provide us feedback, or respond to our request for information - we will collect the
information you submit. In each such instance, you will know what data we collect, because
you actively submit it. We will use the data you voluntarily submit to us for the purposes we
describe in this Privacy Policy, as well as any purposes that we describe to you when we collect
such information.

e. Transactional Information we collect
All transactional data as it relates to bills/ memos created to consumers, purchase
orders raised to distributors, invoices received from distributors, inventory information,
product, brand information will be saved and processed on SnapBizz servers. Data will
also be backed up for disaster recovery.

f. Accept the default GST rates and HSN codes provided in the system and agree to validate / change
them in the system before billing. SnapBizz is providing the  VAT / GST rates and HSN codes for ease of system
use and is not responsible for their accuracy. SnapBizz is not liable for the accuracy of
the VAT / GST rates and HSN codes supplied by default with the system, hence SnapBizz is not liable for error
in any VAT / GST rates calculations and HSN codes.

\n\n2. Cross-Border Transfer
The information we collect is stored and processed on servers in India, Singapore and
may also be transferred to other countries. By using the SnapBizz Services you consent to
the transfer of the information described in this Privacy Policy to locations that may be outside
of the country in which you live, and such places may be in the United States, within one or
more European countries, and/or in one or more countries within Asia, Africa or Australia. If
any provision within this Privacy Policy is held to be invalid or unenforceable in a territory, such
provision shall be struck with respect to such territory and all remaining provisions shall be
enforced.

\n\n3. Uses of Information
In addition to the other uses of your information described in this Privacy Policy, we may
use and process the data we collect for the following general purposes:\na. To provide, protect, and improve our SnapBizz Services, and our systems;\nb. To respond to requests that you may send us such as your request for information;
\nc. To develop new products and services, and other internal business purposes;
\nd. To protect our rights and the rights of our users;
\ne. Any other use we describe at the point where we collect the data.
\nf. You agree to confer on SnapBizz the right to commercially exploit advertising space and time at the store LED / Plasma / TV screen which would include rights for screening / displaying advertisements including slides and advertisement commercials in the store LED / Plasma / TV screen during all the store working hours every day when the store is open .
\ng. You confirm that the advertising rights conferred on SnapBizz supersedes any other rights which You may have granted to any third party prior to the date of signing of this MOU , in respect of onscreen advertising rights  at the store LED / Plasma / TV screen and that in the event exclusive onscreen advertising  rights are granted to SnapBizz , it shall be on all formats and the store owner shall screen the advertisements/ commercials that are provided by SnapBizz from the date of this agreement.
\nh. You agree to grant SnapBizz the right to utilize adequate space up to the limit specified by the store owner (landlord) or other mutually agreed space within the store premises to facilitate promotional activity to be carried out by the advertisers contacted by SnapBizz / their agents, such as product launch / demos / sampling etc.
\nTo the extent permitted by applicable law, we reserve the right to combine the various
types of data that we collect and to combine the data that we collect with anonymous or
aggregated data (e.g., demographic information) that we obtain from third parties or other
sources. We may use the combined data for any of the purposes described in this Privacy
Policy.

\n\n4. Data Sharing
We do not share your personally identifiable information with others, except as
follows: We may share your information with agents, service providers, vendors, contractors,
or affiliates who process the data only on our behalf for the purposes set forth in this Policy
and under terms of confidentiality. We may also share your information as required by law
or in the interest of protecting or exercising our or others legal rights, e.g., without limitation,
in connection with requests from law enforcement officials and in connection with court
proceedings. We may share or transfer your information in connection with a prospective or
actual sale, merger, transfer or other reorganization of all or parts of our business. Finally, we
may also share your personal information where you have granted us permission.

\n\n5.Opt Out
If you do not want us to collect, use, and share the information we describe in this Policy,
please notify us of your decision to opt out, discontinue your use of SnapBizz Services, and
uninstall or clean your devices of any SnapBizz software or licenses.

\n\n6. Accessing and Changing Your Account Information
You can review the personal information you provided to us and make any desired
changes to your username, password, and phone number at any time by logging in to your
account. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, SnapBizz
may, for a time, retain uncorrected, residual information about you in its backup and/or archival
copies of its database. To access other personal information we may have associated with your
account, please contact us through the Contact Us section below. Upon request we will provide
you a copy and/or description of any personal identification information we hold about you within
in a reasonable time and we will correct or delete it upon your request.

\n\n7. Security
We take reasonable steps to protect the personal information submitted to us, both
during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or
method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use
commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its
absolute security. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login and password
information.

\n\n8. Contact Us
Please feel free to contact us with any comments, questions or suggestions you might
have regarding the information practices described in this statement. You may contact us by
writing to us at:
\n\nSnapBizz CloudTech Pte. Ltd
\n#1 Raffles Place, One Raffles Place #39-01,
\nSingapore 048616

\nEffective Date: April 15, 2014

\n\nBy clicking, “I Agree” I have read, understood and
agree to the terms and conditions in this agreement.
</string>
    <string name="check_agreement">Click checkbox to indicate that you have read and agree to the terms presented in the Terms and Conditions agreement</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="reject">Reject</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="terms" translatable="false">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>

</resources>